我超酷的家人
My super-awesome family
提前给我办了一个生日惊喜聚会
was throwing me a surprise early birthday party.
我猜只有我一个人在家
I'm guess I'm the only one at home.
老爸 你怎么能这样
How could you do this?! Dad!
你本该是我的英雄
You were supposed to be my hero!
你真让我失望
You let me down!
或者我今天忘了找电工
Or I forgot to meet the electrician today
修家里的接线盒
to fix our faulty junction box.
各位 我不会找借口
Guys, I'm not gonna make excuses.
我上班真太忙了
I've been really busy at work.
我拉头发刚拉到一半
Well, I was halfway through straightening my hair.
我正在洗
And I was in the middle
攒了三周的衣服
of doing three weeks' worth of laundry.
而我刚才真的写期末论文
And I was actually writing a term paper
灯就灭了 然后 什么
right when the lights went out, and...what?
这不是苏打水啊
This isn't soda.
好了 趁你们还没发表任何意见
Okay, before you guys say anything,
我穿这件衣服是因为我实在没...
I only put this on because I didn't have anything --
看来问题自己解决了
Well, the problem obviously self-corrected,
我早料到了
which I knew it would.
是我修好的
Well, I fixed it.
老妈叫人来修了
Yeah, mom called a guy.
克莱尔 抱歉 我太忙了
Oh, Claire, I'm so sorry. I got busy at work, and --
亲爱的 别在意
Oh, honey, don't even worry about it.
还好冰箱又能工作了
I'm just glad the fridge is up and running.
我把明天的午饭提前备好了
I pre-packed all the lunches for tomorrow.
三明治里的布里奶酪可别化了
I didn't want the Brie on the sandwiches to get runny.
布里奶酪
Brie?
别再剧透了
Don't tell me any more.
要的就是惊喜
I live for the surprise.
老妈 我知道你工作忙 不过
Hey, Mom, I know you're really busy at work, but --
甜心 我绝不会拿这个当借口
Sweetheart, I would never use that as an excuse.
有什么指示
What do you need?
-卖糕饼用的纸杯蛋糕 -好哇
- The cupcakes for the bake sale. - Okay.
我们刚被困在家里
Oh, and since we got stuck here,
没法出门
I couldn't go out and get
给我室友买生日礼物
that birthday present for my roommate.
也没法去干洗店拿裙子
Or my dress from the dry cleaners.
遵命 遵命 遵命
Done, done, and done.
-妈妈最棒了 -抱抱
- We have the best mom ever. - Hugs!
好吧
Okay.
等等 大伙儿 老爸在这呢
Wait, wait, guys. Guys, Dad's here.
老爸 拍一张我们抱老妈的照片
Dad, take a photo of us hugging Mom.
以前我把家事搞砸的时候
Until now, when I'd screw up on the home front,
总可以拿工作当借口
I could always blame work,
可现在克莱尔要经营公司
but with Claire running a company
妈妈这个角色当得前所未有的称职
and being a better mom than ever,
我都能感受到孩子们
I could feel the kids downgrading
对我大失所望了
their whole opinion of me.
从A级老爸变成F级了
I went from an "A" Dad to an "F" Dad.
废·邓菲 菲尔·邓废
Fail Dunphy. Phil Dun-fail.
废利普·很废 邓...
Failip Hum-fail Dun--
我以前说很溜的
No, I had it before.
说"布里"
Say "Brie."
布里
Brie!
我觉得啊
Hey, you know what?
明天我也可以帮帮孩子们
I could do some of that kid stuff tomorrow.
你有开放参观日要忙呢
You've got that open house.
亲爱的 我都跟工作和家庭周旋22年了
Honey, I've been juggling work and family for 22 years
这点事情算什么
and just juggling for 30.
那条裙子我到时候得穿 所以
Well, I really need that dress for an event, so --
交给我
I got it.
明天的任务 拿裙子
Agenda for tomorrow -- One dress,
做蛋糕 买礼物 没了
one set of cupcakes, one present, and that's it.
我记住了 别以为我会忘
I got ya! You thought I forgot.
我3点40就去找警报公司的人来
I will be here to meet the alarm company at precisely 3:40...
今天3点40就该找的
earlier today.
昨晚还没吵够吗
You didn't make enough noise last night?
他哭得我失眠四个小时
With all his crying, I didn't sleep four hours.
我也没合眼
I didn't close my eyes.
感觉像回到我的村子
It was like being back in my village,
警惕土匪来一样
watching for the marauders.
我也不知道哪个更让我惊讶
I don't know what's more shocking --
你原来要站岗放哨还是会用"土匪"这个词了
You standing watch, or knowing the word "Marauders."
别跟我说我小时候
Please tell me I didn't sob all night
因为小毯子不见了哭了一整晚
just 'cause I lost my baby blanket.
嘘 别让他想起来 他现在挺开心的
Shh! Don't remind him. He's happy now.
再说 你小时候连毯子都没有
And besides, you didn't even have a blanket.
咱们以前一贫如洗
We were basically destitute.
怎么 你们家被闪电击中了吗
What, did you get hit by lightning?
还好乔今天约好要跟小朋友出去玩
Thank God that Joe has a playdate.
维吉会来接我们
Vicky's picking us up.
我要让他狠狠玩
I'm gonna make him play so hard
玩到今晚累晕
that he's gonna pass out tonight.
我跟威士忌有个约会
Well, I've got a playdate with Johnnie Walker,
我俩中的一个今晚会不省人事
so one of us is passing out tonight.
好啦 我知道没狗粮了
Yeah, I know we're out of dog food.
我打完高尔夫就去买
I'll pick some up after golf.
她正好可以借此机会减肥 没事
She could lose a couple of pounds, anyways.
还好你没女儿
Thank God you don't have a daughter.
等那孩子一睡着
The minute that kid falls asleep,
我保证那架飞机一定失联
that plane goes Amelia Earhart.
这布置是不是感觉挺低端的
Doesn't this seem a little chintzy?
是啊 咱们可以走了吗
Yeah, can we go now?
不行 还没跟两位新郎问好呢
No, we haven't said hello to the grooms --
还有策划这场婚礼的才子
Or the talented people who planned this wedding.
胡娇·萨尔兹曼的又一力作 伙计们
Another great Pepper Saltzman production, guys.
得了吧 周五中午的婚礼简直俗到家了
Oh, please. What's tackier than a Friday lunch wedding?
给五号桌拿点 番茄酱
Table five needs more...ketchup.
每次摄影师过来
I have to hide my face with a coat
我都得拿外套遮脸
every time the videographer comes around.
想当年
In the old days,
他从不接这么便宜的单
he'd never taken a cheap job like this,
可是同性恋婚礼越来越少了
but the gay-wedding business is drying up.
我们会把便宜婚礼统一办成谢曼·萨尔兹曼婚典
We do the bargain ones as Sherman Saltzman Events,
然而35年前我在卢博克搭上那辆公车后
and I haven't been Sherman
就没用过谢曼这个名字了
since I got on that bus in Lubbock 35 years ago.
都好几个月了才订了另外两场
We've only booked two others in months --
上周亚当和迈克的婚礼
Adam and Michael last weekend
和下周一菲利克斯和乔丹的
and Felix and Jordan next Monday.
周一
Monday.
走开 阴魂不散的
Oh, away, you vulture.
小卡 你会不会觉得有点奇怪
Cam, do you think it's a little weird --
亚当和迈克 菲利克斯和乔丹的婚礼
That we weren't invited to Adam and Michael's
都没请我们 是的 非常怪
or Felix and Jordan's? Yes. Totally weird.
亲爱的 小孩坐这桌
Okay, sweetie, here's the kid's table.
我们该坐哪儿 没有空位了
Where is our table? There are no more tables.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我们要坐那里 65号桌
That's us. Number 65.
我们的朋友呢
Where are our friends?
都不在这里
Not here.
我们是被列入基佬黑名单了吗
Are we on some sort of gay blacklist?
-我不要坐那儿 -你坐那儿
- I'm not sitting there. - You're sitting there.
你好
Hello.
你好 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
记得纸杯蛋糕 礼物 还有裙子
Oh, cupcakes, present, dress.
我记着呢 我马上去办
I remember. I'm gonna get on that
等我先把这边布置完
just as soon as I'm done with my open house.
先问一下 礼物要到哪里去拿
I just wanted to clarify, where am I getting the present?
等一下 菲尔
Hang on, Phil.
我这边在忙
I'm in the middle of something.
等我一下下
Just one second.
你要去百思买商场找斯但 斯坦
I'm -- it's at the Best Buy. Ask for S-Sean -- Stan.
说是邓菲家订的
It's under "Dunphy".
谢谢亲爱的
Thanks, honey.
真不知道你怎么能记住这么多东西
I don't know how you do it all.
爱你
Love you.
那是个提土旁吗
That's a "t"?
人们说要持好家和管好公司
They say it takes a village to raise a family
通常需要很多人齐心协力
and run a company.
原来 要实现这一切
Turns out, it just takes
只需要市场部一个叫本的马屁精
one little suck-up from marketing named Ben.
克莱尔 不知道你有没有听说
Oh, Claire, I don't know if you heard.
他们把克莱默的会议提前到五点了
They moved the Kramer meeting back to 5:00.
-不 -是的
- No. - Yeah.
不行 我要给卢克球队做千层面晚餐
No, I-I have to make a lasagna for Luke's team dinner,
但是我也不能错过这个会议
but I can't miss that meeting.
其实我是厨房好手
You know, I know my way around a kitchen.
因为我妈是个酒鬼
My mom's an alcoholic.
所以我能轻松帮你做好千层面
So I could easily knock out a lasagna for you.
本 你救了我一命
Ben, you are a lifesaver.
我保证不会老麻烦你帮我忙
I promise I will not make a habit of it.
其实我真想一直让他帮忙
I kind of made a habit of it.
淡定点
Calm down.
我们只是翘了两节课
We only cut two classes,
我会用你妈妈的电脑发一封请假邮件
and I'll send an excuse e-mail from your mom's computer.
真不敢相信就因为你给我半个布里奶酪三明治
I can't believe I agreed to ditch with you
我就答应跟着你翘课了
just 'cause you gave me half your Brie sandwich.
不过那里面味道超好的苹果片
Although that party-crashing apple slice
给三明治增色不少
turned out to be a welcome plus-one.
那我们现在可以摊开说了吧
So we can make it official now.
其实我有三个基佬舅舅[包括曼尼]
I have three gay uncles.
是的 我很抱歉 迈尔斯
Yeah, I'm -- I'm sorry, Miles.
不 帮我跟大家道个歉
No, apologize to the guys.
我只是太累了 打不了高尔夫
It's just, I'm too tired to play golf.
该死 忘了买狗粮
Damn it! The dog food!
斯黛拉 你今天走运了
Stella, this is your lucky day.
我和歌洛莉亚第一次约会的时候
Gloria makes this Colombian dish
她做过一道我爱吃的哥伦比亚菜
I loved when we were first dating.
其实那时候我也说过其它的谎
I lied about a lot of things back then.
你在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?!
我花了三天
That takes me three days!
三天来准备这道菜
Three days to prepare!
然后你说你很爱吃
And then you say that you love it,
现在你竟然把它拿去喂狗
and you feed it to the dog?
你还骗了我什么
What else have you been lying about,
杰·肯尼迪·普里契特
Jay Kennedy Pritchett?
斯黛拉吃掉这菜后这周都不能跟我亲亲了
No Daddy kisses till Sunday after she eats this.
对不起 维奇
Sorry, Vicky.
今天孩子们不能一起玩了
We have to cancel the playdate.
乔在车里睡着了 我不想吵醒他
Joe fell asleep in the car, and I don't want to wake him up.
好的
Okay.
杰出去打高尔夫了真是万幸
Thank God that Jay was out playing golf.
上一次乔睡着了我把他忘在车里
The last time that I left Joe sleeping in the car...
亲爱的 乔呢
Honey, where's Joe?
在车里睡着呢
Sleeping in the car.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?!
你不能把小孩留在车里
You don't leave a kid in the car!
你怎么不干脆在他身上放个标志
Why don't you just put a sign on him
再写上"免费土狼食物"
saying "Free Coyote Food"?!
我没见过谁发这么大的脾气
I have never seen anyone so mad.
就算是抢匪 起码你还能跟他对上话
Even the marauders, you could have a conversation with.
"家里有急事"
"Family Emergency."
"叽里呱啦 歌洛莉亚·普里契特"
"Blah, blah, blah. Gloria Pritchett."
然后发送
And send.
我真不想问出口
I hate that I have to ask this,
但你不是真的把"叽里呱啦"打上去了吧
but you didn't type "Blah, blah, blah," did you?
你得放松
You need to chill...
像我女朋友这样
like my girlfriend here.
不 我受不了这个
Nah, I can't enjoy that.
我一直会想到那女孩的爸爸
I just keep thinking about that girl's father.
你能不能别在我妈的电脑上播这玩意
Could you please just get that off my mom's computer?
好吧 这是给你翘课的奖励
Okay. That was your reward for ditching,
但是既然你不喜欢
but if you don't want to...
怎么回事
What "Uh-oh"?
画面卡住了
Uh, it's frozen.
什么
What?!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
就停在这个恶心画面
It froze on that?
你说的"恶心画面"是有名字的
Hey. "That" Has a name.
来 斯黛拉 来吃吧 乖孩子
Here, Stella. Come and get it, girl.
杰 是你吗
Jay, is that you?
是的
Yep.
该死
Damn it.
-该死 -该死
- Damn it! - Damn it!
-我没听见你进屋 -那就好
- I didn't hear you come in. - That's good.
你怎么这么早就回来了
Oh, how come you're home so early?
太累 不想打高尔夫
Too tired for golf.
乔呢
Where's Joe?
在楼上
Upstairs.
我终于把他哄到睡着了
I finally got him to sleep.
她想出去
She wants to get out.
-我来抱她 -不 不 你待在这里
- I'll take her. - No, no, no. You stay here.
-我把她抱出去 -不行
- I'll do it. - No, you can't.
我是说 我们难得有独处的时间
I mean, w-we rarely get times like this anymore.
乔在睡觉 曼尼也去上学了
Joe's sleeping, Manny is at school.
不如我们上楼--
Why don't we go upstairs and --
睡个午觉
Take a nap.
没错
Exactly!
我妈坐她朋友的车
My mom got picked up by a friend.
我们可以开她的车去电脑店
We can take her car to the computer store
在她回家前回来
and be back before she gets home.
她没关窗也没关灯
She left the windows down and the lights on.
有时她也太不注意了
Sometimes, she is so oblivious.
我只要等杰睡着就好
All I had to do was wait for Jay to fall asleep.
我简直是个天才
Genius.
她几分钟内就会打呼的 太简单了
She'd be snoring in minutes. Piece of cake.
我们离得也太远了
We are so far away from everything.
他们上一次敬酒的时候 我在听到声音之前
During the last toast, I saw them clink the glasses
先看到了他们的碰杯
before the sound actually reached us.
婚礼被冷落
Snubbed at this wedding,
其他两对的婚礼也没邀请我们...
not invited to two others...
你究竟做了什么
what could you have possibly done?
对不起 我说了会在吃甜品的时候跟你换位子
Sorry. I said I would switch with you at dessert.
胡娇 胡娇
Oh, Pepper. Pepper.
-你知不知道为什么... -不好意思
- Do you have any idea why... - Oh, sorry.
我正赶着去土豆泥桌
I'm in a mad rush to the mashed-potato bar
补一些 配食
to restock something called...fixin's.
如果你们为我着想的话
If you ever felt anything for me,
就把我扔出窗外吧
you'll push me out a window.
米奇尔 可能...
You know, Mitchell, m-maybe it's...
我不想争论这种事了
Look. I can't have this fight again.
我看见你向他抛媚眼了
I saw you ogling him.
对我来说
Hey, as far as I'm concerned,
我们根本不应该再争论这种事
we never have to have this fight again.
米奇尔 别
Mitchell, stop it.
-怎么了 -偷听
- What? - Eavesdropping?
寻求生意机会
Trolling for business?
你一直这样
You've been doing it
自从开始处理同性恋离婚案件
ever since you started handling gay divorce.
这有点吓人
It's kind of ghoulish.
-吓人 -没错
- Ghoulish? - Yes.
肯定是因为这样才没人希望我们出现
I'll bet that's why nobody wants us around.
就是这样 你就像是同性恋婚姻的死亡天使
That's it. You're like the Angel of Death of gay marriage.
你就像老人家里的猫
You're like a cat at an old-folks' home
在快死的人旁边蜷着
who curls up next to somebody about to die.
他们还配谴责我吗
They're judging me?
菲利克斯和乔丹可是做动物皮草生意的
Felix and Jordan sell fur.
不好意思 我们不小心偷听到你们在偷听我们
Sorry. We couldn't help overhearing you overhearing us.
我们的一些朋友正准备分手
Some friends of ours are breaking up,
他们需要一位好的离婚律师
and they need a good divorce lawyer.
你有名片吗
Do you have a card?
我们不小心偷听到你们在说
We couldn't help overhearing you
你们偷听到你们偷听你们
talking about you overhearing you overhearing you.
你真的在接同性恋离婚案吗 我们都不知道
Are you really doing gay divorces now? We had no idea.
我刚偷听到你们偷听...
I was just overhearing you guys overhearing...
我的天 这叽里呱啦的
Good Lord, it's like a game of Princess Telephone.
这是我的名片 我想问一下
Here is my card, and just to be clear,
你们没有人知道我在接同性恋离婚案吗
none of you knew I was doing gay divorces?
-不知道 -有点意思
- No. - Oh, interesting.
太有意思了 婚礼上玩得愉快
That's very interesting. Have a good time at the wedding.
原来这份吓人的职业
Well, how about this ghoulish profession
除了你之外所有人都觉得没问题
that no one seems to have a problem with except for you?
对不起 但你一直都有点愤世嫉俗
Look, I'm sorry, but you've always been a little cynical,
我担心你看多了这些婚姻失败的案子
and I was worried you seeing all these marriages collapse
会让你不由得往那个方向发展
would push you further in that direction.
不 不 恰恰相反
No, no, it's the opposite.
在这些不幸夫妻身边
Being around all these unhappy couples
让我对我们所拥有的更加感激
makes me even more grateful for what we have.
太感动了 你...
That's so sweet. Are...
你确定这不是你酒喝多了随便说的吗
are you sure that's not the cash bar talking?
当然不是
Of course not.
你是我所遇过最好的事
You're the best thing that has ever happened to me.
你也是我所遇过最好的事
And you're the best thing that's ever happened to me.
小卡
Oh, Cam.
也许这才是没人希望我们出现的原因
Maybe this is why nobody wants us around
因为我们去到那里都那么感性
is because we cause an emotional scene everywhere we go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我永远都不会成为他想要的儿子
I'll never be the son he wants.
我们会变成什么样
What's to become of us?
现在可真是难倒我了
Well, now I'm stumped.
没错 那可以冷藏东西
Yep. That refrigerates stuff.
它们都可以
All of them do.
俗话说得好
But you know the saying...
所有好的开放参观日都要在两点准时结束
All good open houses must come to an end by 2:00 on the dot.
可是我妈妈还在来的路上
Oh, but my mom's still on her way.
她要来给首期
She's giving us our down payment.
你嫁给一个鼓手的时候就知道要怎么做了
You knew the rules when you married a drummer.
我们妨碍到你了吗
Are we keeping you from something?
一"拍"都没有
Not one "beat."
我有个主意
I have an idea.
要不我们用刚出炉纸杯蛋糕的香味
Why don't we greet your mom
来迎接你妈妈吧
with the smell of fresh-baked cupcakes?
材料在这里
The ingredients are in here.
威尔 拿好搅拌器
Will, grab a whisk.
我会在你们俩撒糖霜之前回来
I'll be back before you two are frosting.
我在去取的路上 斯坦
I'm on my way to pick it up, Stan.
我会在5...
I'll be there in like 5...
至45分钟到
to 45 minutes.
好吧 纸杯蛋糕
Okay. Cupcakes.
礼 不 不
Pres...Oh, no. No.
该死
Damn it.
纸杯蛋糕烤糊了
The cupcakes burned.
闻起来还不错
Well, it still smells homey.
给了妈妈一个机会好好看看
And it gives Mom a chance
这里最先进的烟雾报警器是如何工作的
to see how well this state-of-the-art smoke alarm works!
跟我来 妈妈
Come with me, Mom!
让我带你看看这幢好房子的其他部分
Let me show you around the rest of this dream house!
看到没 连熨衣服都是一种享受
You see, even ironing is a delight here,
你可以感受到从滑窗外
where you can feel a cool breeze
拂进来的微风
wafting in from the open sliders.
我了个去
Mother nature!
你瞧 专属的礼物包装室
Huzzah! Your own gift-wrapping room,
就像富人和名人家里的一样
just like the rich and famous.
席拉 借我根手指
Sheila, finger.
来吧 好的
Go right ahead. There we go.
不好意思我来晚了 但别担心
Sorry I'm late, guys, but fear not.
一份生日礼物
One birthday present.
包装得像婴儿礼物一样
Wrapped in baby-shower paper.
一件熨好服帖的礼裙
One crisply pressed dress.
上边有一个之前没有的褶子
With one big pleat it didn't used to have.
至少我们知道你为什么迟到了
At least we know why you were late.
看起来你好像是从一个着火的面包店里
Looks like you rescued those cupcakes
救出来的那些纸杯蛋糕
from a burning bakery.
别担心 妈妈做了那些备用的蛋糕
Don't worry. Mom made those on the off chance
以防万一你搞砸了 果然不出所料
what everyone knew was gonna happen happened.
她还给我买了那条新裙子
She also bought me that new dress.
对了 希望你留了发票
Oh, and I hope you kept the receipt,
因为妈妈给我买了备用的礼物
because Mom bought a backup.
好吧 别因为妈妈低估我就生她的气
Well, don't be mad at your mom for underestimating me.
我们怎么可能生气呢
Oh, how could we, when she made us
她还给我们做了手工搅拌冰激凌
this fresh hand-churned ice cream?
怎么可能
Yeah. What?
对了 你知道我们该怎么做吗
Oh, you know what we should do?
我们应该给她发一张我们吃冰激凌的照片
We should send her a picture of us eating it.
看来我回家至少还能给你们拍张照片
I guess it's a good thing I came home when I did.
还是我来拍比较好
It'd be better if I did it.
你做了冰激凌
You churned ice cream?
是的 孩子们喜欢吗
Yeah. Did the kids like it?
-她们爱死了 -太棒了
- They loved it. - Great.
但是她们知道我不会做冰激凌
But they know I can't make ice cream.
我是喝了三杯血腥玛丽之后看了购物广告
I bought that churn out of a SkyMall catalog
才买的那个搅拌器
after three Bloody Marys.
它在我车库里一块布下面盖了六年了
It's been sitting under a tarp in my garage for six years.
你可得多收敛收敛了
You've got to dial it way back.
你为什么要害怕跟生气呢
Where is this fear and anger coming from?
你会害我们被发现的
You're gonna get us caught!
一开始你就知道这是有风险的
You knew the risks when we started this.
我只是说我们最近有点马虎了
I'm just saying we're getting a little bit sloppy.
所有那些不可能的差事 精致的三明治
All the impossible errands, the fancy sandwiches.
接下来的几天只要在全麦面包上涂点
Just slap a little tuna on whole wheat
-吞拿鱼就够了 -你说什么 不行
- for the next couple of days. - What? N--
先等事情平息一段时间
Just until things cool off.
好吗
All right?
我只是想让你开心点
I was just trying to make you happy.
你不会阻止我的 是吗
You're not gonna stop me, are you?
咖啡车只在大厅服务到四点
Coffee cart's only in the lobby until 4:00.
谢谢你 克莱尔
Thank you, Claire.
谢谢
Thank you.
这太没面子了
This is mortifying.
修它的人会看到我们看的东西
Whoever we ask to fix this
觉得我们是变态
is gonna see what we're watching and think we're pervs.
那个人就不会
Not that guy.
卢克
Luke?!
你好啊 玛丽安
Hi, Marianne.
你都长这么大了
You're so grown-up now.
是啊 这是曼尼
Yeah. Uh, this is Manny.
玛丽安以前是我们的保姆
Marianne used to be our babysitter.
还记得以前你跟我求婚吗
Remember when you asked me to marry you?
"我外[爱]你 玛丽安"
"I wuv you, Marianne."
很高兴见到你 我们得走了
Well, nice to meet you. We should get going.
好吧 再见了 给家里带好
Okay. Bye, guys. Best to your family, okay?
我真想看看知道你堕落成这样之后
I'd like to see the look on Mawianne's face
玛丽安脸上会是什么表情
if she knew what a degenerate you turned into.
下一个
Next.
我来吧 凯尔
I'm here, Kyle.
又见面了
Hello again.
我能帮你们做什么
How can I help?
我们要怎么办 我妈随时都会回来的
What are we gonna do? Mom's gonna be home any minute.
"亲爱的 你看到我的电脑了吗"
"Hola, papi. Have you seen my computer?"
"当然了 妈妈 就在那
"Oh, sure, Mom. It's over there,
有个没穿衣服的女孩正在里边
where that naked girl's entertaining
取悦她学校的篮球队员呢"
her school's basketball team."
我跟艾丽克斯视频一下
I'm face-timing Alex.
她会知道怎么办
She'll know what to do.
怎么了 卢克
What's up, Luke?
电脑出了点小问题 屏幕不动了
Computer glitch. The screen's frozen.
-让我看看 -还是不要了
- Let me see. - I'd rather not.
所以是黄片
So porn.
好吧 我先把这篇论文写完
Well, I just have to finish this paper.
我一小时后打给你
I'll call you in an hour.
你好呀 小可爱
Oh, hey there, cutie pie.
谢谢夸奖 艾丽克斯 但你能快点写
Thank you, Alex, but could you please hurry
-然后给我们回电话吗 -我是和
- and call us back? - I was talk--
她知道我对她而言就是禁果
She knows I'm forbidden fruit.
我确信她因此更被我吸引了
I'm sure that's half the appeal.
杰
Jay!
Jay?
你醒了多久了
How long since you have been up?
我醒了没多久
Oh, about a minute before you.
你能帮我个忙吗
Oh, can you do me a favor?
你能不能去看看洗的衣服
Can you go and look at the laundry?
我觉得好像洗好了
I think it's done.
当然了 但是亲爱的 我睡得有点不舒服
Sure, but, honey, I think I slept kind of weird.
你能去楼上帮我把加热垫拿下来吗
Could you run back upstairs and get me my heating pad?
斯黛拉为什么拼命要去那里
Why is Stella going crazy there?
斯黛拉 快走开
Stella, get out of here!
你们好 大家都怎么样啊
Hi, there. How's everybody doing?
斯黛拉怎么了
What's up with Stella?
你们俩去哪了
Where have you two been?
那是我的电脑吗
Is that my computer?!
-别打开它 -别打开它
- Don't open that! - Don't open that!
-那是乔的飞机吗 -别开门
- Is that Joe's plane? - Don't open that!
看起来这有不少未解之谜啊
A lot of unanswered questions here, it seems like.
我看我们都先各退一步
Why don't we all just...take a step back?
放轻松
Nice and easy.
好了 所以
Okay, so...
我现在要出去散个步
now I am going to go and take a little walk.
卢克和我要上楼做作业
Luke and I have some homework to do upstairs.
而我 要去小朋友的房间
And I'm going... to the little boy's room.
除了我们这里 他们每桌都拍了照片
They have taken pictures at every table but ours.
因为他们的摄影师不是黛安·阿勃斯
Because their photographer isn't Diane Arbus.
不然还有谁愿意记录这场《热夜之梦》
Who else would want a record of this Fever Dream?
你还要吃这个吗
Are you gonna finish this?
他们没准备工作餐
They didn't budget a staff meal.
我们穷是我们自己的错
It's our own fault we're poor.
我们有钱的时候
When we had money,
把钱都花来雇喝醉的水手了
we spent it all on drunken sailors.
你是想说"像喝醉的水手一样花钱"吧
You mean "like drunken sailors"?
当然了
Sure.
胡娇 你走之前
Pepper, before you run off again,
为什么所有人都当我们像贱民一样
why is almost everyone here treating us like pariahs?
你们不是冰冷地拒绝了
Well, you didn't help yourselves by the cold way
前两个婚礼邀请吗
you declined those last two wedding invitations.
我们没有收到邀请啊
We didn't get those invitations.
但我收到你们的回复了啊
I got the RSVPs myself
给亚当和迈克以及菲利克斯和乔丹的回复
to Adam and Michael and Felix and Jordan.
只在"无法出席"那一栏画了个大叉
Just a big "X" In the "Will Not Attend" Box.
没有理由 没有礼物
No excuse, no gift.
你当然可以引起别人的不快
Of course you put people off.
只是这并没什么风度
It's just not classy.
这些布丁得放了多少天了
How old are these pudding cups?!
过来 亲爱的
Come, carino.
在大厅里有个自动售货机
There's a vending machine in the lobby.
如果我在它旁边倒下了
If I lie down next to it,
你会把它推到我身上让我死吗
will you push it over on me?
为什么我们回复了从未收到的婚礼邀请函
How could we RSVP to wedding invitations that we never got?
参加聚会的人们 让我们跳起来吧
Okay, party people, on your feet.
如果我提前离开 你俩有意见吗
You guys cool if I take off?
不 亲爱的 你怎么了
No. Sweetie, what's been going on with you?
自从我们到这你就想着走
You've wanted to leave since we got here.
你们都去跳舞吗
Hey, y'all coming?
管它呢 去跳吧
Might as well.
走啦 莉莉 我们去跳舞
Come on, Lily. Let's go dance.
不 不跳 这太尴尬了
No! No dancing. It's too embarrassing.
不是的 你跳得非常棒 亲爱的
No. You're a good dancer, sweetie.
不是说我 说你们呢
Not me. You two.
什么
What?
你不喜欢我们跳舞 为什么
You don't like our dancing? Why?
还问为什么
Why?
你们跳得并不好 所以我讨厌婚礼
You're not good. That's why I hate weddings.
等等 莉莉 你是不是回复了一些婚礼邀请
Wait, Lily, did you RSVP to some weddings
却没有告诉我们
and not tell us?
是的 惩罚我吧 给我禁足吧
Yes. Punish me, ground me.
我就是不想看你俩跳舞的丑态了
I just can't watch it again.
你绝对会被惩罚的
Oh, you're gonna be punished.
米奇尔 等一下 我理解她的感受
Mitchell, wait. I know how she feels.
我俩真的令你那么难堪吗
Did we really embarrass you that bad?
是的 我依然爱你们 但
Well, yeah. I mean, I still love you, but...
为什么你的肩膀在动
Why are your shoulders moving?
我们一直知道
Well, we always knew there
我们俩有某些地方让你厌烦
would be something you didn't like about us.
我们只是很高兴
We're just glad that
令你不快的竟是我们如此擅长的事情
it's something we're so good at.
如果有人问起 就说我是和你们一起来的
If anybody asks, I'm with you.
是的 加文 我准备好了你要的
Yes, Gavin, I got everything you asked for,
而且我马上到
and I'm on my way.
我要给老板做这么多跑腿的事
All these errands I have to do for my boss.
我发誓如果要不是因为我
I swear, if it wasn't for me,
他什么也弄不好
he'd never get anything.
海莉 拜托 我正试图弄清
Haley, please. I'm trying to figure out
你妈妈是如何自己完成那么多事的
how your mom's getting all these things done by yourself.
当海莉给了我一个倾听自己心声的机会
When Haley finally gave me a chance to hear myself think,
我突然想到了
it hit me.
会不会是克莱尔请了个助手
Could Claire be using an assistant?
我决定追溯今天她说的每件差事
I decided to retrace every errand she allegedly ran today
并且计算时间
and time it out.
从早上九点到下午一点半她在开会
She was in meetings from 9:00 A.M. To 1:30,
假设她有九十分钟来买海莉的裙子
leaving her a 90-minute window to buy Haley's dress,
到商场找斯坦取艾丽克斯的礼物
see Stan at Best Buy for Alex's present,
然后开车回家
then speed home,
然后她可以开始烤纸杯蛋糕
where she could start baking the cupcakes,
从车库里把冰淇淋搅拌器搬出来
drag the churn in from the garage,
搅拌 包装 上霜
churn, wrap, and frost,
她还剩不到八分钟在学校放学路段拥挤的时刻
leaving her a scant eight minutes at school pick-up time
加速赶回公司参加三点的员工会议
to race back for her 3:00 staff meeting.
即使在她路上全部十四盏交通灯都是绿的
Even if all 14 traffic lights on her route were green,
这项任务也会是
this task would be...
不可能完成的
Impossible.
我不知道冰激凌是谁做的
I don't know who made that ice cream,
但是爸爸我即将在一个满是霜冻的大碗掀起风暴
but Daddy was about to churn up a frosty bowl
这个碗就叫"妈妈是个大骗子"
of "Mom's A Big Fake."
本 你还在这里做什么
Ben, what are you still doing here?
我只是正在为孩子们做三明治
I'm just making sandwiches for the kids.
不用担心 他们绝不会知道
Don't worry. They'll never know.
我用的是商店卖的高德干酪和家用芥末
I'm using store-brand Gouda and this domestic mustard.
不 你不懂
No, you don't understand.
我丈夫可能会在任何时候回家来
My husband could be home any minute.
你必须得走了
You've got to leave.
这是什么
What is this?
"谢谢你的建议 老妈 太有用了"
"Thanks for the advice, Mom. It worked great."
什么建议
What advice?
你把手机落在了你桌上
Oh, well, you left your phone on your desk,
当你开员工会议时艾丽克斯发来短信
and Alex texted when you were in that staff meeting.
她看起来很沮丧 所以我处理了一下
She seemed really upset, so I took care of it.
大概就是男孩子那些事
It was, like, boy stuff, whatever.
本 我们必须停止这样做了
Ben, we got to stop doing this.
没事的 我只是说了你会说的话
No, it's fine. I just said what you would have said.
但我什么也没说
But I didn't say anything.
我根本没在我女儿身边
I-I wasn't there for my daughter at all.
我忙得焦头烂额尝试做一个完美妈妈
I-I'm so damn busy trying to be the perfect mom
以及完美的老板
and -- and the perfect boss,
但我却把对我来说最重要的工作外包了出去
but I'm outsourcing the one job that means the most to me,
我很怀念这份工作
and I really miss it.
我怀念当个妈妈
I miss being a mom.
即使我只是个一般的妈妈
Even if I'm a so-so mom
很少有时间做一个没烤熟的金枪鱼三明治
that barely has time to make a soggy tuna-fish sandwich, I...
-那你应该回归到这个角色 -是的
- Then you should get back to that. - Yeah.
我应该回办公室了
And I should get back to the office.
不 本 你不需要这么做
Oh, no. Ben, you don't have to do that.
太晚了
It's so late.
不晚 我必须这么做
No, I do.
我妈妈和她的新男友有个约会[炮]
My mom's got a "date" With her new boyfriend,
所以我得到样板间里过夜了
so I'm gonna crash in the showroom.
谢谢你
Thank you.
在你打开这个之前 我只想说
So, before you open this, I just want to say
这不是我通常会看的东西
this is not the kind of thing I'm usually in to.
少扯了
Let's not.
顺便说一下 只有他在看
It's all him, by the way.
我也信
No kidding.
别打开来让我看到啊
Oh, don't show it to me!
CTRL+Alt
CTRL-Alt-Ew.
天啊 请告诉我修好了
Oh, God. Please, tell me it worked.
修好了
It worked.
人人留学【免费办理】
震撼上线，赶快登陆
www.rrliuxue.com
给你们提个醒
Just so you know,
不是所有女人都是空虚的女色情狂
women are not all vacuous nymphomaniacs
等着诱惑每一个路过的男人
looking to seduce every man that crosses their path.
再见 脏[下流]小男孩
Bye, you dirty little boy!
所以她到底是不是在诱惑我
Kind of a mixed message right?
我会跟她谈谈的
I'll talk to her.